sanmina.com 2018-12-30

# SANMINA CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY

                           SANMINA CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY
                                  Effective date: May 25, 2018
       This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) sets forth the privacy principles that Sanmina
Corporation and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Sanmina”) follows with respect to the
processing of Personal Information (as defined below) of its potential, current and
former customers, suppliers, vendors, business partners, website visitors, visitors to
our facilities, job applicants and independent contractors. Sanmina collects, stores,
processes and discloses Personal Information as permitted by applicable laws,
including the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union. This Policy
describes how we collect, use, disclose and otherwise process Personal Information
about you when you visit our website at www.sanmina.com (“Site”), submit Personal
Information directly to us on the Site, inquire about our products or services or apply
for employment or provide independent contractor, temporary staffing or other
services to us. We collectively refer to these activities, together with the operation of
our Site, as “Services”.
       In this Privacy Policy, “us”, “we” and “our” refers to Sanmina and “you” refers
to persons covered by this Policy.
I. PERSONAL INFORMATION SANMINA MAY COLLECT AND HOW IT IS USED
        “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or
identifiable individual. Sanmina collects, stores and processes the following Personal
Information concerning its potential, current and former customers, suppliers,
vendors, business partners, website visitors, visitors to our facilities, job applicants
and independent contractors using the Services for the purposes described below, to
the extent permitted by applicable law.
Type of Personal Information Collected,       Purpose of Such Collection, Processing
Processed and/or Disclosed                    and/or Disclosure
Potential, current and former
customers, suppliers, vendors, business
partners, website visitors and facilities
visitors
Contact details (e.g. name, street            To provide you with the Services,
address, email address, phone number,         including by allowing you to create and
employer, job title)                          manage your account, providing you with
                                              information about our products and
                                              Services; to communicate with you and
                                              respond to your inquiries, comments and
                                              requests; to solicit business or present
                                                -1-

Type of Personal Information Collected,    Purpose of Such Collection, Processing
Processed and/or Disclosed                 and/or Disclosure
                                           potential business opportunities;
                                           marketing calls; sending you marketing
                                           communications; and advertise to you on
                                           other websites; to understand and
                                           analyze the usage trends and preferences
                                           of users of our Services; to improve the
                                           Site; to comply with legal process; to
                                           maintain our contractual relationships
                                           with our customers, vendors and business
                                           partners
Government issued identification, country For facility security measures, including
of citizenship, profile photos, video      issuance of visitor passes and access to
images                                     our facilities; legal and regulatory
                                           compliance; promotional purposes, with
                                           consent
IP address, browser type, device ID, OS    To analyze the effectiveness of our
(operating system) type, information on    communications, including marketing
actions taken on our Site, dates and times campaigns; to tailor our Services, content
of actions                                 and communications to you; to create and
                                           publish content relevant to you; to
                                           understand and analyze the usage trends
                                           and preferences of users of our Services;
                                           to improve the Site and the Services, such
                                           as by assessing how many users access or
                                           use our Services, which content, products
                                           and features of our Services most interest
                                           our visitors, what types of offers our
                                           customers like to see and how our
                                           Services perform; to improve our products
                                           and services; network and/or data
                                           security; to enforce legal rights and
                                           comply with legal process
Personal Information directly related to   To analyze the effectiveness of our
accessing or using the Services (e.g.      communications, including marketing
confirming whether an email recipient      campaigns
opened an emails or whether a Site visitor
clicked on a link), where permitted by
law
                                            -2-

Type of Personal Information Collected,   Purpose of Such Collection, Processing
Processed and/or Disclosed                and/or Disclosure
Job Applicants
Name and contact information (e.g.,       Process applications for employment
name, street address, town/city,
state/province, country, email address
and phone numbers)
Identification information (e.g., social  Verification of right to work in a given
security number, taxpayer identification  jurisdiction
number, national identification number
and passport and driver’s license
information, including birth date and
place); legal residency information, work
permit and visa information
Gender                                    Government reporting and where no other
                                          identifying details are provided
Nationality and ethnic origin             Government reporting and compliance
Veteran or military status                Determining compliance with government
                                          programs and preferences relating to
                                          veteran or military status
Personal information contained in cover   Making employment decisions
letters, resumes and employment
applications, including employment
related and salary information
Current employment status                 Verification of information contained in
                                          employment application
Current or past salary, where permitted   Formulating employment offers
by applicable law
Consumer, credit and criminal             Assessing suitability for employment in
background information (when permitted    certain positions
by law and with applicant consent)
Disability information                    Assessment of ability to offer reasonable
                                          accommodation
Results of drug testing when requested    Assessing suitability for certain positions
                                           -3-

Type of Personal Information Collected,    Purpose of Such Collection, Processing
Processed and/or Disclosed                 and/or Disclosure
and obtained in accordance with            in the Company (e.g. truck drivers and
applicable law                             heavy equipment operators)
Temporary Workers (employed by
staffing agencies or other third parties)
Name and image, job title/job code,        Facility access (i.e. badges)
plant, department, location, supervisor,
temporary employee identification
number/badge number; home address,
birth date, phone number, emergency
contact details, medical practitioner
contact details (i.e. name, address,
phone number), next of kin and pre-
employment health questionnaire
Contact information (i.e., name, street    Authentication and access to Sanmina IT
address, town/city, state/province,        systems and applications, such as email
country, email address and phone
numbers); identification information
(e.g., social security number, taxpayer
identification number, national
identification number and passport and
driver’s license information, including
birth date); legal residency information,
work permit, visa information; date of
hire; gender; temporary employee
identification number; job information
(e.g. job code, job title, job grade,
location, supervisor)
Independent Contractors
Name and contact information (i.e.,        Payment of fees for services; preparation
name, street address, town/city,           and delivery of income tax documents;
state/province, country, email address     authentication and access to Sanmina IT
and phone numbers); identification         systems and applications, such as email
information (e.g., social security number,
taxpayer identification number, national
identification number and passport and
driver’s license information, including
birth date); legal residency information
Bank account details (e.g. account         Payment of fees for services; confirming
                                            -4-

Type of Personal Information Collected,       Purpose of Such Collection, Processing
Processed and/or Disclosed                    and/or Disclosure
number); Financial/credit                     compliance with Sanmina policies for
information/insurance information             independent contractors
Work permit, visa information; date of        Authentication and access to Sanmina IT
hire; gender; job information (e.g. job       systems and applications, such as email
code, job title, job grade, location,
supervisor)
       Note: Sanmina does not necessarily collect all of the above-listed information
from any particular individual using the Services or covered by this Policy. In case we
use Personal Information for reasons other than those listed above, we will provide
you notice of such uses or obtain your consent, in each case if required by applicable
law.
II. SOURCES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT SANMINA MAY COLLECT
       The above-listed Personal Information may be provided directly by you to us by
email or in online submission fields that you complete on our Site (including our Site’s
Partner Connect portal) or on the websites of third parties we direct you to. In
addition, we may receive Personal Information about you from third party marketing
partners and databases, and we may combine this information with other Personal
Information we maintain about you, if permitted by applicable law and, if required by
applicable law, with your consent. Finally, we may also receive Personal Information
about you from other sources such as employers, business partners, public databases
and other commercially and publicly available sources.
       One way we collect Personal Information on the Site is through use of cookies
and similar technologies. You may set your browsers to provide notice before they
receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie.
You can also set your browsers to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas
of the Site may not function properly.
       We may also use analytics providers such as Google Analytics, which use
cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the
Services and report on activities and trends. These services may also collect
information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources. You can
learn about Google’s practices by going to
https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/, and opt out of them by
downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
                                               -5-

III. HOW SANMINA MAY USE PERSONAL INFORMATION
     Sanmina may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:
     ● To provide you with the Services, including by creating and managing your
        account, providing you with information at your request, and creating and
        publishing content relevant to you.
     ● To communicate with you and respond to your inquiries.
     ● To tailor our Services, content and communications to you in order to provide
        you with a better experience.
     ● To place marketing calls, send you marketing communications, and advertise to
        you on other websites, such as LinkedIn. For example, we may send you an
        email to alert you about product upgrades, special offers, updated information
        and other new products and services. Our marketing may be tailored to you,
        based on information such as your interests and preferences (which we may
        deduct from your interactions with our Site and email campaigns).
     ● To operate, evaluate and improve our business and develop new products and
        services.
     ● To understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of users of our
        Services, to improve the Site, and to develop new products, services, features,
        and functionality (including anonymization of Personal Information).
     ● To enforce legal rights and comply with the law.
     ● To comply with an order from a government entity or other competent
        authority.
     ● To prevent or address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights,
        property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or
        damage.
     ● To protect our rights, prevent fraud and/or comply with judicial proceeding,
        court order, or legal process served on Sanmina.
     ● To manage our customer, vendor and partner relationships.
     ● For other purposes for which we provide specific notice at the time of the
        collection of the information.
IV. SANMINA’S GROUNDS TO PROCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION
     Sanmina processes Personal Information on the following grounds:
     ● You have consented to the processing of your Personal Information. For
        example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our use of cookies and similar
        technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
     ● We need your Personal Information to provide you with the services and
        products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries.
     ● The processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation.
     ● The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you.
                                               -6-

    ● We or a third party, have a legitimate interest in using your Personal
       Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal
       Information for the purposes set forth in the table above.
V. HOW SANMINA MAY DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION
       Sanmina may disclose the Personal Information we process about you to its own
employees, to third parties retained by Sanmina to provide Services or to auditors,
attorneys and other professional advisors, insurance companies and brokers and
financial institutions, in all cases only as needed to fulfill the purposes described in
this Policy or otherwise disclosed to you at the time of collection. When required by
applicable law and as appropriate, we enter into data processing agreements or
similar agreements with the third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the
Personal Information that is processed. If Sanmina is involved in a merger, acquisition,
financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of Sanmina
assets or transition of service to another provider, Personal Information may be
disclosed or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law or contract.
Sanmina may also disclose Personal Information in order to comply with the law, legal
process and enforce legal rights.
VI. HOW SANMINA PROTECTS PERSONAL INFORMATION
       Sanmina maintains administrative, technical and physical safeguards that
Sanmina believes are appropriate to protect Personal Information against accidental
or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized
disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the
Personal Information in Sanmina’s possession.
       Sanmina completes periodic reviews of its databases, and has established
specific time limits for data deletion, taking into account the type of data and its uses,
mandatory retention periods and the statute of limitations.
VII. RIGHTS AND CHOICES
       a. Potential, current and former customers, suppliers, vendors, business
           partners, website visitors and facilities visitors
       You may choose not to use the Services, in which case no Personal Information
about you will be collected or processed. Most web browsers automatically accept
cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you
prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Site. If you receive
an email from us, you may opt out from receiving electronic marketing
communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided within each electronic
communication.
       b. Job Applicants and Independent Contractors
                                                 -7-

       Job applicants may choose not to provide Personal Information to Sanmina.
However, to the extent it is not supplied, Sanmina would not be able to assess the
suitability of such persons for employment and therefore to employ such persons.
Similarly, we would not be able to enter into agreements with independent
contractors who do not provide us with the Personal Information needed in order to
retain them and pay them for their services.
       c. Temporary Workers (employed by staffing agencies or other third parties)
       Sanmina collects only limited personal information from temporary workers
who are employed by staffing agencies or other third parties and who are assigned by
such third parties to work at our facilities. Should such persons not provide such
information to Sanmina, we would not be able to permit them to work at our facilities
or to access our IT systems.
       d. Consent
       Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of sensitive
Personal Information. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal
Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When
you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent
withdrawal.
       e. Right of Access, Deletion and Transfer
       In certain jurisdictions, you may have the right to (1) request access and
receive information about the Personal Information Sanmina maintains about you, (2)
update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, (3) restrict or object to
the processing of your Personal Information, (4) have the information blocked,
anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, (5) transfer your Personal Information and (6)
lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection authority in the country in which
you are located, if applicable.
       Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements.
You may exercise the rights specified in this section by contacting us as specified
below.
VIII. DATA TRANSFERS
       Personal Information that Sanmina collects may be stored, processed or
transferred to any of Sanmina’s or third party vendors’ locations or computer systems,
wherever located. Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not
have the same data protection laws as the country in which in which the data was
originally collected. Regardless of where Sanmina stores, processes or transfers
Personal Information, it will protect that information as described in this Policy. If
you are located in the European Economic Area, we comply with applicable legal
                                               -8-

requirements to provide adequate safeguards for the transfer of Personal Information
to countries other than the country where you are located. We may transfer Personal
Information to countries for which adequacy decisions have been issued, use
contractual protections for the transfer of Personal Information, such as the European
Commission's Standard Contractual Clauses, or rely on third parties’ certification to
the EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks where applicable. You can obtain
a copy by contacting us as provided in the “Contact Us” section below.
IX. LINKS TO OTHER SITES
       This Privacy Policy covers the privacy practices of Sanmina and it does not
cover the privacy practices of third parties on their websites and other features. Any
information you provide on third-party sites or services is provided directly to the
operators of such sites or services and is subject to those operators’ policies, if any,
governing privacy and security, even if accessed through the Services. To the extent
any features or linked websites you visit are not owned or operated by Sanmina, we
are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of theses third-parties.
X. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
       From time to time, Sanmina may amend this Policy. When we do, we will post
an updated version of the Policy. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will
notify you here.
XI. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
       Residents of California have the right to request a disclosure describing what
types of personal information we have shared with third parties for their direct
marketing purposes, and with whom we have shared it, during the preceding year.
You may request a copy of that disclosure by contacting us at privacy@sanmina.com.
XII. CONTACT US
       If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Policy, or if you
would like to exercise your rights in relation to your Personal Information, please
contact us using the following contact information:
       Sanmina Corporation
       Email: privacy@sanmina.com
       C/O Human Resources Department
       2700 North First Street, Building 1
       San Jose, CA 95134
       United States
                                                -9-
